Вот так встреча, Русинян!
Сколько лет, сколько зим...
Ты всё ещё играешь в это корейское безобразие?
Конечно играю.
Замечательня. А то я беспокоилась, что ты пропал нявсегда.
Ты всё ещё экзальтируешь меня, Некохиме-сан.
Хотя под юбкой у тебя нехилый сюрприз.
Ах да, говоря о том, что случилось между нами, я это пережил.
Более того, это переросло в своего рода убеждение.
Убеждение?
Да. «Эскапируй от реальности изо всех сил».
«Реальность и игры не имеют ничего общего».
Некохиме-сан, а ты тут какими судьбами?
Давненько о тебе не было ни слуху ни духу.
Да на работе нявалилось всего.
Но сегодня один чел помянал игру ИРЛ, и я подумала тряхнуть стариной.
Кулстори бро.
Принятно снова встретиться, Русиян.
[ЛВЛ. 03: Думал, игры и реальность не имеют ничего общего?]
Ты чего здесь зависаешь?
Очевидно же, чтобы уважить своего господина с утра пораньше.
Эм, Тамаки-сан, похоже, что ты ещё не до конца разлогинилась из игры в реальность.
Что ты делаешь? Прекрати.
Шо?
Не «шо», а «что». И да, ты говоришь «господин»
будто горничная какая.
Вот как? Ну тогда…
Пора вставать мой...
...жеребец.
Игноришь меня?!
Хмм... Не думаю, что твоя харизма достаточно прокачана,
чтобы тебе открылась опция с такой фразой.
Ашта? Неужели я запорола персонажа неудачно распределив статы?
Что у них там за ролевые игры?
У-ударь меня.
Здорова.
Здоровей видали.
Ну, я пойду.
Давай.
Нисимура-кун, могу я иметь Момент ?
Нисимура-кун, ты и Тамаки-сан уже няшились под хвостик?
Н-нет, до этого у нас ещё не дошло!
Вы же неплохо ладите?
Полагаю, что да.
В таком случае будь нежен с ней.
Тамаки-сан создаёт впечатление человека, у которого не так много друзей.
До недавних пор она почти не ходила в школу.
Наслышан, ага.
Госёин-сан...
О, Лид… Президент студсовета
О, Нисимура Хидеки-кун.
Учитель Саито, я по вопросу, который мы с вами обсуждали вчера…
Ах это… Прошу извинить, но меня уже занял литературный клуб.
Не разрешите нам хотя бы использовать ваше имя де-юре?
[Клуб изучения средств взаимодействия в онлайновых играх]
Q_Q мой милый Русиян [Enter]
QQ_ мой милый Русиян [Enter]
QQ мой_ милый Русиян [Enter]
QQ мой ми_лый Русиян [Enter]
QQ мой милый_ Русиян [Enter]
QQ мой милый Ру_сиян [Enter]
QQ мой милый Руси_ян [Enter]
QQ мой милый Русиян_ [Enter]
QQ мой милый Русиян [Enter]_
Тебе необязательно надиктовывать вслух.
А? И правда же…
Азаза! Кручу-верчу!
Збс, го сегодня инстанс к мегавулкану Блюмке?
Одобряю. Всем подобрать себе шмот.
Ура!
Эй, Ако, дай-ка глянуть твой эквип.
Пожалуйста, не стесняйся.
В-всё очень плохо.
Чеита?
Мы идём к мегавулкану, почему у тебя весь шмот с сопротивлением к воде?
Я ношу этот сет не снимая, с тех пор как ты, Русиян, подарил мне его.
Ненене, надень что-нибудь на фаеррезист!
Эээ? Но мантия служителя огня такая уродская.
Ты у нас зациклена на внешнем виде?
И что у тебя за стик как у девочки-волшебницы?
Когда ты бьёшь им мобов, он светится и спавнит звёздочками!
Такое то мимимишество!
Так вот кто пол-экрана постэффектами заполонил!
Вуш! Намекаете, что мой шмот это лоу?!
Не то чтобы «лоу»...
...ты будто на бал собралась.
У меня в сундуке есть жезл добродетели, могу тебе одолжить.
У меня уже есть такой.
Так юзай его!
Тебя уже накрыло, Лидер?
В этой мантии меня бы никто замуж не взял.
Сагрил одного!
Збс, сейчас мой посох Умейбо ваншотнет этого…
Что такое, Швайн? Зачем ты меня трогаешь?
Мы же договорились, что премиальный шмот под запретом, забыла?
Хм, но таком случае мне вообще нечего использовать.
ДАФУК? Одни только хайлевелные спеллы за тонны нефти?!
Лидер, чтобы я не видел как вы юзаете предметы купленные за реал.
Не командуй тут! Я президент этого клуба и ваш гильдмастер!
Завали.
Цените все, как папа ловко орудует мечом!
Не вижу ничего принципиально нового.
Шу-тян досталось всё веселье.
Ээх... Дайте и мне встать в победную розу.
Обходись своими силами.
Ещё одна волна!
Да что ж такое? Ок, ваша взяла, не буду пользоваться премиумом.
Но тогда я буду юзать магические атаки этого посоха.
(пусть я и бафнула его за реал)
Пресикс Тувин!
Пресикс Тувин…
Лидеру трындец.
Сильными атаками ты агришь их на себя!
Вот тебе и победная поза!
Будь у меня мой премиум, я бы уже уложила всю пачку...
Ако! Ну тупи! Оживляй её!
Так так... У меня все бинды перемешались.
Куда подевалась иконка воскрешения?
«Воскрешение» тут! «Хил» тут!
Ах! Русиян, ты — ювелир!
Хух... Такого потного данжа у нас ещё никогда не было.
Да, но к середине мы приноровились, и наша эффективность возросла.
Не потому ли, что вместо Ако её перса контролил Нисимура?
Грамотно тащил, Русиян.
Похоже, что сегодня от меня было больше пользы, чем обычно.
В-вот как? Хорошо тебе.
Уже довольно давно хожу в школу без единого прогула,
хотя чую, что скоро снова захиккую.
Хорош гибать уроки. На второй год не завернут?
Как не крути, Русиян, но я сяду тебе на шею,
так что можно вообще бросить школу.
Палехче. Я на такое не подпишусь.
Вут? Не хочешь жену-домохозяйку?
Если уж выбирать, то я бы предпочёл вырвырвыр.
Ась? Чо сказал?
Варуювонакилми.
Чего? Что ты там мямлишь?
Сюткина натравлю!
Чо приуныл, Русиян?
Да нет, похоже, я уже привык к тому, что ты называешь меня «Русияном». Такие дела.
Ой, прости, Нисимура-кун.
Зайдём ненадолго?
М? Ты чего?
Такое ощущение, будто зависаем где-нибудь в LA, согласись?
Но к сожалению это реальность.
Со стороны мы вглядим как жених и невеста небось.
Да кто так может подумать?
У нас для этого даже возраст неподходящий.
В лучшем случае, мы похожи на влюбл…
Снова вечереет. Тебя не хватятся?
Не думаю. Моих родителей то и дома нет.
O RLY?
Иначе мне бы нельзя было гамать всю ночь напролёт.
Тамаки-сан создаёт впечатление человека, у которого не так много друзей.
Закат будто нарисованный.
Двинули по домам?
Офк.
[Клуб изучения средств взаимодействия в онлайновых играх]
Может немного передохнем?
Стоило Ако придрочиться к хилу, как мы стали реже сливаться не по делу.
Нужно было только подобрать ей нормальный эквип.
У меня появилось срочное дело.
Ты по-маленькому?
Как пойдёт.
Так, на чём мы там оста…
Вут? Как это понимать?!
Шу-тян, тебе так идёт!
Шу, мочи!
Ашта?
Откуда у меня стручок порея? Да ещё и с таким дамагом!
Я неплохо вложилась в него.
Не трать деньги на всякую хрень!
Закончим на сегодня.
Отлично сыграно, Русиян.
Ты тоже в этот раз неплохо отыграла.
Русиян назначил меня любимой женой!
Дык вот, мне одной кажется, что в этом клубе нет смысла?
Что не так?
Изначально мы собирались сделать что-то, чтобы как-то решить проблему с Ако.
Так то да.
И похоже, что вместо этого, грань между игрой и реальностью стала лишь прозрачнее.
Задорно же, чего заморачиваться?
Нет, тут есть о чём забеспокоится.
Лидер?
К сожалению у этого клуба осталось не так много времени.
Что?
У нас нет куратора. А без него,
у нас нет разрешения на деятельность клуба.
Так что его роспуск лишь дело времени.
Хотелось бы достичь нашей цели до того, как это произойдёт.
Nekohime-san!
Oh, Rusian!
Um, I could use a little advice.
Hmm, I see.
She absolutely cannot distinguish
between real life and the game.
I get it. I just heard a similar tale
from someone else close to meow.
This girl is, how shall I say? At risk.
One false step, and she could
have had a really hard fall.
Rusian, you're quite a guy.
Huh? You think so?
Have faith in yourself meow!
Leave it to someone out in
the world. That cheers me up.
Um, if it's okay, I'd like to ask
your advice again sometime, please.
But of course.
Ako... I mean, Tamaki-san...
Come sit down here for a minute.
Huh? Is something the matter, Rusian?
I'm not Rusian. I'm Nishimura.
Huh? Oh, right, Nishimura-kun.
This club will end soon,
so I'm going to say this again.
The game and reality are separate.
Tamaki-san, in the game, you and I are married,
but at school, we're ordinary classmates.
From here on, let's treat
each other like regular friends.
Also, when it comes to people
you only know in the game,
and who you haven't actually met,
you shouldn't let your guard down.
Rusian, did someone say something to you?
Huh?
You met someone, right?
And they said something to you, right?
Was it a woman?
No, no, no, it wasn't!
I see. So it was a woman.
No, it wasn't!
Rusian, a wife can tell at a glance
when her husband is unfaithful.
I'm not being unfaithful!
Could I ask for her name?
--Why?
--I want to pay my respects.
No, don't!
Why not? I just want to thank the person
who is helping my husband out.
Of all the things you've ever said,
Ako, that is the scariest.
You just don't know...
...when you're beaten! My anger
is euphoric right now, even for me!
Your Japanese is taking a weird turn, there.
And so, she saw through me in a second.
Rusian, you're so easy to read, after all meow.
I saw you.
Wah! A-Ako!
You like that woman who says "meow," huh?
Rusian, is that kind of woman
the girl of your dreams meow?
Don't you do it, too!
That person is just an acquaintance.
Remember, the cross-player I
mentioned telling that I loved?
Rusian, that's who you
told you loved... you say?
I'm so jeal-- This is outrag--
I mean, what an awful person she is!
Your true feelings are pretty obvious.
Break my pure Rusian's heart, will she?
I'll teach that woman a lesson!
Cut it out, dummy!
Bothering me may be one thing,
but I'm not going to let you
bother Nekohime-san, too.
Rusian...
You read me? I mean it this time.
I understand.
Well, I have some business to
take care of, so I must be going.
Huh? H-Hey, hold on...
Say, Nishimura-kun,
is Tamaki-san not here today?
Huh?
She was in the game last night, right?
Same as always-- Ah, it's Ako!
What is that girl up to?
"Good morning"
"Rusian"
Why aren't you at school?
I had a bit of important business
to handle, so I took the day off.
What important business?
An offline meeting.
Offline meeting?
I don't know anything about it.
With who?
It's a personal one-one-one,
with someone that I know.
Someone you know? In LA?
Yes.
Is this someone that we're acquainted with?
I don't think so.
What? I didn't think there was
anyone you knew here, besides us.
One of your girl friends?
The person told me that he was a man.
I haven't actually met him
in person yet, though.
Huh?!
An offline meeting with
a man she doesn't know?!
Hmm...
H-Hey, don't do it! It's too dangerous!
He's right. And you've got
Rusian anyway, don't you?
That's true. I do have a husband named Rusian.
So then...
But that's only in the game, right?
The game and reality are separate, right?
Tell me, Rusian, what's the difference
between reality and the game?
Hold on, Ako. You're not
sounding like yourself today.
I'm leaving.
That's okay, right, Rusian?
Yeah.
Suit yourself.
Hey!
Do you mean that, Rusian?
Are you sure about this?
What's the problem?
Ako is finally acknowledging that
the game is separate from reality.
The purpose for this club
has officially been achieved.
Everything is all good, isn't it?
Rusian, what's the difference
between reality and the game?
Damn it!
What are you doing?!
What do you mean?
Ako's offline meeting is at 18:00 tonight.
Schew managed to get it out of her.
18:00?
It's happening in front of
Maegasaki Station, same as before.
You have to hurry and go stop her!
I... don't have any right to.
Huh?! Are you still talking like that?
What do you mean, "right"?!
She's your wife, isn't she?
How is she my wife?
That's only in the game, right?
In real life, she's just a friend.
Just like she said.
What's your problem?!
You're so lame! You really suck!
I didn't think you were this big a turd of a guy!
Oh, shut up.
You do like Ako, don't you?
Then that's good enough, isn't it?
Go and stop her.
Are you really going to let the
girl you like walk into danger?
Rusian--I mean, Nishimura
Hideki-kun, the way I see it,
just as Ako confuses the game
and reality too much,
you also keep reality and the game
too separate, don't you?
I do?
Sure, Rusian and Nishimura Hideki are separate.
So are Ako and Tamaki Ako.
But Rusian is there inside you.
There are feelings of affection
for Ako there inside you.
That's not something I can go along with.
Why not?
Because it's more than just that!
After meeting the real Ako, talking to her,
touching her,
I've come to like the non-game Ako, too.
It's not the Ako in the game that
I'm concerned about right now--
it's the real-life Ako!
I'm worried about her!
I don't want her to get hurt!
Really?
Yeah. It's true, all right.
The game and reality are different!
Good enough. You've just given
yourself your own answer.
So hurry and get going.
Yeah!
Such basket cases, huh? The both of them?
Absolutely.
Ako!
Rusian?
As your husband, I don't approve of you
having offline meetings with strange men!
Things may be different in real life,
but in the game, you're still my wife!
Rusian...
Rusian... is Nishimura-kun?
Huh? Saito-sensei...?
This is Nekohime-san.
Huh?!
H-Hold on!
N-No, you're wrong.
Nekohime-san is actually an older man.
No, you can't fool these eyes!
Ever since I met you yesterday,
I knew you were female!
And when I invited you out here,
you end up being Saito-sensei!
Could it just be a coincidence?
She's right. I am Nekohime.
Huh?!
I knew it!
Yesterday, I talked to Ako-san--
I mean, Tamaki-san, in LA.
Huh? Nekohime-san is Saito-sensei?
Then, Nekohime-san really was a woman...
Which means that I... proposed to Saito-sensei?
I'm sorry. It creates too much trouble,
so in the game, I pass
myself off as a cross-player.
No, um, just a moment...
This is taking some time to process...
How dare you toy with pure Rusian's emotions?!
You witch!
I don't care if you are a teacher. As his wife, I...
...will have vengeance!
Hey, what do you think you're doing?!
Move, Rusian! I can't kill her!
And, as a result,
I now present to you the advisor
for the Modern Communication
Electronic Game Club, Ms. Saito.
Having accepted Goshoin-san's
threat--invitation,
there was no choice left to me but
to come aboard as your advisor...
What do you mean, no choice left to meow?
I-I mean, I was happy to!
Brutal.
Well, we couldn't just let
the club end the way it was.
I won't let that "meow" woman
come anywhere near my Rusian.
You should think some more
about what you've done.
You're lucky this didn't
blow up into something huge.
Thanks to Nekohime-san, that is.
All right! Since it's come to this,
I will work hard as the club's advisor.
However, I do have one condition.
Condition?
All club members must come
to school as much as possible.
Okay, Tamaki-san?
Eh?
U-Understood.
Very well.
And you know, now we can all
play the game together again.
Ah, yes, that's right.
Oh, yeah, by the way, Rusian,
you should come and say hello
to my parents sometime soon.
I'm not doing that.
Huh?! Then, I should come to
your house to pay my respects.
I told you...
The game and reality are separate!
"I thought her secret wasn't going to get out?"
Now it's time for your lecture.
If it had been anyone, but me,
this would have been terrible.
I mean, attacking someone you've never met--
I'm sorry meow!
Stop doing that meow!